thank you Rick it's so humbling this is
not about me this is before I begin I
want to take a shortcut on ginseng
search and what do our job for
nominating me for this recognition you
know until yesterday I was kind of
curious about this Cleveland
International Hall of Fame war
recognition but today you know this
evening I understand it let me tell you
know let's let me tell you about the
entire world let me break it up two
different words the first word is
Cleveland and I think that is the best
place in the whole world
I'm sorry my sister is my sister is here
my brother annoys me and my other sister
is here and my other brother lives here
down and ties it is not about the city
it is about the people who we met in
this community
let me start about the city two of my
three kids live born in this city
two of my girls be kept lawyers in this
city all my kids found their spouses in
this city what more I can ask for but
let me tell you my kids they all went to
public school Cleveland Public Schools
Orange Public Schools and they have a
teacher she taught them many of their
mothers not only that she was there
Egypt but she was the predator
she was the priest for the two of my
girls who got married and blessed them
as well
time and how many parents get this kind
of you know privileged to have a teacher
many kids and that is where I told I
told you about my kids been born here
just few weeks ago my fourth
granddaughter was the city of Cleveland
as usual I was traveling I was in India
my wife was in California looking after
my three other granddaughters and this
was indeed a very difficult pregnancy
she delivered at 34 weeks we were away
we found an obstetrician not only that
she served as a physician but she served
as a proxy parents for my daughter and
my son-in-law making most difficult
decisions of our lives that is for
children is all about and that is what
this command is all about fortunately my
two month old granddaughter is also in
this audience celebrating this
nomination
[Applause]
also you know Cleveland offers the best
health care in the whole world and I'm
not going to introduce you my patients
will come all the way from India to the
table etc but let me tell you that
physicians who are here with me
prompting them today it is just an
amazing place I am working there for
last 37 years and that's not even
important
my father had eight surgeries performed
at the Cleveland Clinic to by toby Cosmo
what by Victor Fazio you may have heard
those things and my father ripped up to
here 91 my mother was scared at the
Cleveland Clinic and she lived up to 93
years old with that calculation I am
going to be hundred and five my wife is
going to be 125 years
they care for her better than be
offended so that is worth the keep
including this pot and let me tell you
my friends have heard this thing over
and over again but I'm so proud to say
that I am the true Cleveland Indians
the next word in this award is
international and one of my friends is
in the audience he likes Oxford
Dictionary divide up this word
international to be is very intriguing
you know that means foreign that means
different and it is a very durable world
you know it lasts for generations
my son is election day as a state
representative for the city of Cleveland
and both of us both of us take this word
very seriously the word International is
our inspiration in hi hope it is your
inspiration as well very proud
and Boxley Hall of Fame before I give
here
I almost heart the Hall of Fame is for
athletes or it is like rock and roll
hall of fame or jib Toby would get into
this when Mike Smith me get into the
Hall of Fame I brought my favorite
players considered identities but I
would like to thank Deborah for making
this love thing for a common person or
complement like myself I'm nothing more
than a common individual and I
appreciate this opportunity to serve the
community the last but not the least
today Laurie you gave me your name you
included me in your friend and once
again you included this common man into
your culture and
I truly appreciate that I was just
performing my civic duty that's all I
did
it was my honor when you asked me to
take care
it's what I have learned from you it's
very simple and some of my patients out
here in the audience is that you cannot
heal the body you cannot kill the body
without touching the soul and that is
what my hope to continue to it
once again I thank my entire complete
family my entire payment community for
all fortune for being here and I
sincerely hope I sincerely hope that my
last 37 years of contributions are only
worth your - thank you